Previously on Ghost.
My family is in serious trouble.
Everything's taken care of.
Thank you, Tariq.
You know I'll do anything
for you and that baby.
- I told you to handle it.
- Fuck this.
Fuck you. Get the fuck down there.
Wait! Please don't.
Tariq killed Zion?
How the fuck would you know that?
I cleared the server.
That's the only copy.
I'll hold on to this. You go home.
You get me the leverage
I need to go against Noma,
and maybe I change this murder
to a fucking accident.
An accident?
- I know.
- What the fuck really happened?
Tariq St. Patrick and Monet Tejada
said you're after me.
Common enemy.
Why not common goal?
You sure this is
the guy who killed Kamaal?
Run ballistics on this gun.
We find the match that killed Kamaal,
and then we get Tate off our asses.
- Now you good with that?
- Yeah, I'm good with that.
I need you to show me
that you can do better
than your parents.
I just want us to be together again.
I ain't forget the
promise I made to you, ma.
It's time for Carter and Noma to go.
Being that Cane and Noma
are getting married,
I say that's the day we
take our shot at her.
And Detective Carter?
Confession at Saint Michael's.
You gotta do better than them
punk ass Russians, my guy.
Get your ass in the car.
B, what the fuck did we just do?
This motherfucker had us on tape.
The fuck you gonna do now, Tariq?
I now pronounce you man and wife.
I need you to choose.
- Where's Cane?
- He's still inside.
Where the fuck are your cousins?
Noma got 'em.
We'll go around back.
You take the fuckin' side.
Monet is the only person,
the only one that
was there to protect me.
Monet is my blood.
I'm never goin' against my mother.
Fuck yourself.
- Get me out!
- Ma!
My babies.
It's okay, ma. Wait.
No, ma!
Ma!
Don't do this. Please don't.
Wake up,
mami. Wake up, wake up, wake up.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Did you see who shot Monet?
No.
Guests told me
Monet wasn't at the ceremony.
When did she get here?
I don't-I don't know.
So your bride
ditches you and then disappears.
- And you don't know why?
- Yeah, you heard me.
I said I didn't see anything.
We just found the body lying there.
Can you think of any reason
why someone would want to hurt Monet?
- Nah.
- That's surprising,
since she's been accused of being
a murderous drug dealer
who had that shit comin'.
What the fuck you say?
How about y'all stop treatin' us
like we're fuckin' criminals
and find out who killed my mother.
Huh?
Do your fuckin' jobs!
It doesn't seem like you're
fuckin' helpin' me, B.
Okay, well, if he arrested you,
it would have been over.
I had to think fast.
Tariq, how are you gonna
get out of this one, brother?
- Shut the fuck up.
- This is you thinking?
Tariq.
I didn't see you come up
with a fucking plan, now, did I?
Yeah, well, my plan is to dust
this motherfucker off the board.
Tariq, hold the fuck on. Tariq!
Okay brother, you gotta
think about this now.
You kill me and my video of you
and fuck boy killin' Zion,
Well, that goes public,
and your life is over.
You keep me here,
and the entire NYPD will not stop
until they fuckin' find you.
It's just a matter of time.
Either way, you're fucked.
So I'm gonna ask you again.
What the fuck are you gonna do?
Attaboy.
The fuck are you going?
Yo.
Davis, we're fucked.
Carter has a video of me
and Brayden killin' Zion.
Well, it gets fucking worse.
- Monet's dead.
- What?
What the fuck are you talkin' about?
Hell no, that's not possible.
Well, her body's in the morgue
full of bullet holes.
So I say it's real fucking possible.
And Noma managed to slip
through the Tejada's fingers.
My money's on she did it.
Fuck.
So I'm just stuck here with Carter
until I figure some shit out.
Carter has something on you.
Then you need to get something on him.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Level the playing field.
Exactly.
No way a cop that dirty doesn't
have skeletons in his closet.
A'ight. I'll call you back.
Wait. Hey.
Be careful, okay?
We can't afford another fuck up.
Yo, Effie, B.
- Talk to him, Brayden.
- Shut the fuck up!
Shit is getting worse.
Monet is fuckin' dead, y'all.
- What?
- Yeah.
- How?
- Got shot.
Davis sayin' Noma did it and got away.
Fuck.
Seemed like she was bulletproof.
Cane and the Tejadas are
probably so fucked up right now.
Fuck Cane and the Tejadas.
Noma's comin' for us.
You know that, right?
Either way, we need to do
somethin' all right?
We have his key.
That means we need
to get in his house,
get that video and destroy it.
Then we could kill him.
If we don't get that video,
we gotta...
we gotta come up with some other
dirt on the motherfucker's name.
Fuck.
Fu-
I can't believe she's gone.
Shit don't feel real.
Monet held us out our whole lives.
What are we supposed
to do without her?
I don't know.
I mean, ain't this is
what y'all wanted?
Nigga, what the fuck are
you talkin' about?
You know what I'm talkin' about.
Y'all went in there to kill
Noma behind my back.
What the fuck was y'all thinkin'?
What were we thinkin'?
Cane, we did it to save our family.
What fuckin' family?
Every time y'all do some shit
and leave me out,
it gets fucked up.
You left yourself out
when you decided to go play
house with Noma.
Oh, I know you ain't talkin'.
Ma had to beg me not to kill
you after what you did.
For all I know, this shit tonight
was you two tryin' to finish
what you started.
Y'all probably sent
Monet in there to die.
You know, we went in there
lookin' for you.
What the fuck happened Cane, hmm?
How is it that Monet is dead
and you're sittin' here
right in front of me?
- Dru, stop!
- No, no, no, fuck that shit.
Monet is dead,
because she went in
tryin' to save you.
So Monet is dead, because of you!
She should have just let me go.
Monet would never give up
on you like that.
You know that.
Ma told me not to trust that bitch.
Maybe I could have stopped her.
Maybe it is my fault that mom is dead.
Fuck.
Noma killed Monet, period.
And Ma wouldn't want
us arguin' like this.
We are all we have left.
What's in the past is the past.
Let that shit go.
We decide what happens next.
So let's finish what we started.
We track Noma down
and we kill that bitch.
Hey, Tariq, let me ask
you a question, man.
Um, how do you-how do you do it?
How do you get your friends
wrapped so tight around your
little finger that they, uh,
well, they willin' to lose
their lives for you?
Hmm?
And how do you live with the fact that
everybody you know ends up dead?
Shut the fuck up!
Hey, listen, I'm gonna
do you a favor, all right?
These cuffs, they got
my shoulder's feelin' mad tight,
so why don't you come over here,
work out some of these knots,
and I'll think about droppin'
that first degree murder
charge down to a second.
I mean, maybe, just maybe,
that way you'll get out of prison
with enough time to have
your own babies to disappoint.
Shut your motherfuckin' mouth!
Ah, Diana's baby was your baby.
I thought it might be.
I wasn't sure.
I'm sorry for your loss, brother.
Then again, the life you lead
means constant loss.
So, you got to know that by now, right?
By the way, how's your mother?
- Shut your fuckin' mouth!
- Oh, oh fuck.
Oh.
Yo, I think Carter's,
like, obsessed with
his dead wife or something.
Yo, you think he wears
her clothes on the weekends
- on like, some psycho shit?
- Oh, shit.
- I found it.
- You did?
Oh, fuck.
Look at this.
- Can-can you delete this?
- I don't think so.
Carter has access to
his work computer from home,
- but it's read only.
- So we can't get rid of it?
Not unless you have someone
on the inside.
It's the only way.
Fuck.
Well, unless having
a creepy ass shrine
dedicated to your dead wife
is a crime,
we don't have shit.
Wait.
This is everything that
Carter looks at, at work
and all the files he accesses.
But for some reason, he keeps
going back to this one file.
Holy shit, Kamaal Tate.
That's Rashad Tate's brother.
The cop that was killed.
This doesn't make any sense.
The official investigation was closed
when they determined
it was a Russian hit.
Like some retaliation
for that warehouse raid.
But, that isn't right
because I was there.
They wiped the Russians, so they ran.
They weren't lookin'
for some fucking cop to kill.
Okay, but cops lie.
What the fuck else is new?
Can we prove it?
Carter signed off on this himself.
It's not much, but...
- It's all we really got.
- Right.
Shit.
Yo!
Please tell me you
deleted that fucking video.
Carter's got it on
a computer at his office.
There's no way to delete it from here.
Fuck.
But I think we got
something else we could use.
Let me guess, no luck.
I wonder if-if your wife
knew that she married a killer.
What the fuck'd you say?
I mean, Denise.
Did she know the truth?
The truth?
Yeah.
The truth that you're a
fuckin' psychopath with a badge.
I mean, did Denise ever see
the real you, my guy? Like-
- Shut up, shut up.
- Is that why she's gone?
Is that why she died?
Don't fuckin' say her name again.
Look, how many innocent people
lost their fuckin' lives
because you had to cover your ass,
Hm?
Does it really make you feel powerful
that you got Diana beat so fuckin' bad
that she lost her baby, man.
That was your baby.
And on the bright side,
we spared the world of
another degenerate criminal.
Fuck.
Mm.
Too soon?
You seem to forget,
that I'm the one that helped
you clean up Diana's mess.
Because I see the
bigger fucking picture, Tariq.
Nigga, you covered that Felicia shit
to cover your own fuckin' ass.
Yeah, I'm sure that wasn't
the first time, either.
Kamaal Tate, he was on your
task force, right?
One day he's alive,
next day he's gone.
What happened?
Oh, he must have found out
your little secret, right?
The Russians did that.
Just like they did me
and Monet, right?
God damn.
Denise really did marry a cop killer.
Fuck you.
That shit crazy Detective Carter.
Noma.
Any word?
The police have questioned
the man we have
stationed at your home.
So far, you do not appear
to be a suspect,
but you are wanted for questioning.
Well, I'm more concerned about
those fucking Tejada children.
The look on Cane's face.
We have a flight scheduled
for this afternoon,
but we need to leave now.
Okay, I have new passports
for myself and Anya
at a safe deposit box that
we can pick up on the way.
Let's be ready in five minutes.
- Noma.
- What?
First Lombardi in Italy, and now this.
You are destroying
everything our family built.
Father should have never
brought you into this business.
Well, if you had the balls that I do,
maybe he wouldn't have needed me.
Don't fucking touch me!
Don't fucking touch!
Mom, what the fuck is going on?
Sweetheart,
we don't have time for this.
- We're going to Lagos and then-
- Lagos?
- Yes.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
I've never been to Nigeria.
My life is here.
And now we're in danger here, Anya.
What part of that
don't you understand?
Any of it, Ma.
I don't understand any of it.
And unless you start telling me
the truth about what's going on,
I'm not going anywhere with you.
You've been lying to me
my entire life.
To keep you safe, Anya.
Mom, the only one putting
me in danger, is you.
And you know what makes it even worse?
Is you had the chance
to tell me the truth,
but instead, you lied right
to my fucking face.
It's not dad's drug business, is it?
It's yours.
Wait outside.
Listen to me.
Every choice I've ever made-
Oh my God. Okay.
Please, mom. Enough of the bullshit.
- Listen to me.
- Can you just admit it, please?
Everything you do is
to protect yourself.
Because, God forbid,
the world find out you were
a fucking drug dealer.
I don't care about the world, Anya.
I care about you.
I was ten years old
when I learned of our family business.
A rival gang came into
our home one day
when my father was away.
I didn't know what was happening.
Chinedu took me by the hand
and pulled me outside,
but not before I saw what
they did to my mother.
As I got older,
I vowed to never be in a
position so vulnerable again.
And anybody who stood in my way,
would come to know
the same pain that I knew.
But I never wanted that for you, Anya.
I never wanted you to know
the-the kind of monsters
that truly own this world.
- So you became one yourself?
- I did what was necessary.
And was it necessary for dad to die,
because of your business?
Yes.
Your father died
because he got in my way.
I didn't mean it like that.
No, I knew exactly what you meant.
- Anya, pl...
- Get the fuck away from me.
It should have been you that died.
Okay, take a moment.
Calm yourself down.
We'll talk about it when I return.
But when I get back,
we're leaving here,
whether you like it or not.
I'll drag you out by the fucking
ankles if I have to.
Yo! Shit.
B was right.
Carter did kill that cop, Tate.
Yeah, how do we make that work for us?
We can figure out how
he covered his tracks.
Could use that.
Maybe it'll guarantee
him not burning us.
I gotta meet with Davis, though.
Davis?
Does he know something we don't?
I mean, he could get us the
records of the crime scene.
Who fucking knows
how long that's gonna take?
Listen, that's Rashad Tate's brother.
You know how fast he wants
to figure out
who the fuck killed him?
I mean, it's something.
Go.
We'll handle bad lieutenant over
here, all right?
Yeah.
Cane?
We found Noma,
and I got Bronze and them
ready to ride for us.
It's time.
- No, no please!
- Where's Noma?
She's not here.
- Please don't shoot.
- Stop fucking lyin'!
She's not here, I swear.
- The house is empty.
- Noma's not here.
- Fuck it.
- No, no!
What are you doing?
Makin' sure Noma don't leave
the country.
What we got?
A whole lot. Davis came through.
This look familiar?
Ballistic reports of every
officer involved shooting
where you pulled the trigger.
Is that your plan?
To prove that I'm a cop
who holds his own?
No, more like prove that every
single bullet you fired out
of your service weapon
matches the ballistic evidence
from the Kamaal Tate crime scene.
But since the reports get
delivered through you first,
you thought you could cover up
the truth by making it seem
like the Russian's gun
matched the Tate murder.
But you couldn't go back
to your old files.
They're right there
in black and white.
The ballistics match up.
You pulled the fuckin' trigger.
Wait, so, so that means
that we also have the gun
that you used to kill Tate,
right?
It's tough.
This whole time,
you think you was fuckin' untouchable?
You got cocky.
Now, look, we got everything
we need to destroy your ass.
The second we send this to
Rashad Tate, you're done.
I'ma let you make a decision.
And you're kinda smart.
So, what's it gonna be, Don?
You wanna press your luck or what?
What do you want?
Mm.
We all walk away from this.
Nobody even knows we were here.
That Zion video never
sees the light of day,
and neither will this evidence.
And after that,
we all live to die another day.
How that sound?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
A'ight then.
Uncuff him.
Anything?
- No?
- No, nothing.
She's nowhere on the grounds.
She may have been taken.
I want everyone out looking for her.
Anywhere the Tejadas
have ever been spotted.
You know, we don't know for
certain it was them.
Of course we fucking do.
This feud you have with the
Tejada family
is not worth you losing your own.
We'll find Anya,
but first we have
to get you to safety.
I'm not leaving without her.
You're not staying here either.
- Watch me.
- Move.
Yes sir!
D.J. and Lifts said
they're ready to head back home.
You stay low y'all.
We ain't got no time to be
catchin' no case or no bullets.
All right, y'all go.
You already did enough.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
All right, love y'all
Love you.
- Love you too.
- Y'all be safe.
Look, did Anya say anything yet?
- She will.
- Okay.
So now what the fuck we gonna do?
I said she'll talk.
And then what Cane?
We've already blown
our cover with Noma.
Even if Anya tells us where she is,
she's still gonna see us comin' now.
Y'all, maybe there's another way.
- This shit better work.
- It will.
I'm sorry for your loss.
I know what she meant to you.
Yeah. Condolences.
Monet was a real one.
And we appreciate that.
But we gonna need y'all
to put something real
behind those words.
We need Anya to give up
Noma's location.
I can help with that.
I just need something in return.
See, I told you this motherfucker
don't care about Monet.
Cane, just hear him out.
Look, Monet will always
have my respect,
all right?
Noma deserves everything
that's comin' for her.
I'm with you on that.
But that don't change the fact
that I still got to deal with Carter.
A'ight.
What do you need?
He got us on video Killin' Zion.
- Ah Fuck.
- Yeah.
Place was rigged with cameras.
- Tariq, I am so sorry.
- It's all good.
You know, I bought us some time, though.
We just need someone
to get into the station
and delete the video.
Think you could use
your access to Carter
to get into his office.
Maybe.
But how am I supposed to delete
the video from the database?
Thumb drive.
Put it in Carter's computer,
you run the program,
it'll wipe everything.
He wouldn't even know.
What y'all think?
It's a means to an end.
I'll do this.
You better make sure Anya talks.
Definitely.
Anya.
Tariq.
W-what are you doing here?
You should keep
your voice down, all right?
I'll explain everything later.
Wait, are you involved?
How did you even know I was here?
Look, your mother killed Monet, okay.
And if you don't get the fuck
out of here right now,
they're gonna come kill you next.
- Come on.
- What are you talking-
Let's go Anya. Just trust me.
Come on. Let's go.
Hey!
Look, nobody's following us,
all right.
Now, you wanna tell me
where I should be takin' you?
Can you like, tell me
what the fuck is going on?
Look, it doesn't matter, all right?
I need to get you
to your mother. That's it.
Why? Who-who the fuck is she to you?
What does she tell you?
No, no, no more fucking secrets
and lies.
Tell me what you know.
All right. I work for Noma.
Okay?
So you've been lying to me
this whole time, too?
Look, I didn't know who
you were at first, Anya.
- Yeah.
- I was surprised, too.
Look, I know what it's like
to find out the truth
about your parents.
That's why I never said anything
to you in the first place.
Why do you do it?
Do what?
The same thing your dad did.
The same thing that got him killed.
The same thing that got my dad killed.
Tariq, if our lives can't amount
to anything more than the sum
of our parents mistakes,
then what's the point?
We can choose to be better
than them, all right?
Not make the same
mistakes that they made.
Not if they don't give us a choice.
Like, I don't think I want to
have anything to do with my mom.
Well look Anya, right now,
the best chance you have
of making it out of this shit alive
is if I bring you to your mother.
So you don't really have a choice.
I'm sorry.
Of course.
No! Fuck it.
Fine, fine. Fuck it.
I have an address.
It's like an emergency meeting spot,
if I was ever separated from my mom,
If she didn't know where I was,
it's the only place she'd go.
Thank you, officer, I got him.
What are you doing here, Dru?
Look, man, I'm just here
to talk to Carter.
Is he around?
No,
I haven't seen him since last night.
You know anything about that?
No, man. I'm just here to talk to him.
Look, it's really important,
about the business.
I just saw Carter
coming through the back.
He was headed to evidence.
All right, wait here. I'll find him.
I gotta talk to him in private.
Put him in Carter's office.
Sit and don't touch anything.
Fuck!
Come on.
Yo.
Hey.
Didn't see you come in.
Everything okay with-
what happened last night?
Yeah, I just... I'm fine, I'm fine.
What is it?
Dru Tejada is here asking for you.
You think he knows about the setup?
Dru's here now?
Yeah, he's waiting for you.
Shit. Come on.
Fuck you doin' here?
Why are you here?
I know you worked with Noma
to try and take out Monet.
I'm just here to make
things right between us.
Tell me where Noma is.
I'll kill her,
and we're good.
You want to prove yourself to me?
I need Tariq dead first.
Then I get you Noma.
It looks like there's nobody here.
There's cameras everywhere.
She'll see me when I get out.
Anya, wait.
Just because I chose the life I live,
doesn't make me my father, you know?
I mean, you could make
your own decisions.
Could live your own life.
You don't have to be like Noma.
You know what, I'm never gonna
be like my mother.
But I don't want to be
like you either.
Anya, sweetheart, I feel terrible.
Oh my God! Oh my God!
- Diana, what the fuck?
- Now she knows how it feels.
The fuck?
Let's go. Let's go.
Anya, everything is going to be okay.
Just hold on. Just hold on.
Anya, Anya! Look at me.
Anya!
I told you Anya was
gonna lead us to Noma.
Hurting Anya wasn't part
of the fuckin' plan.
What was you thinkin', D?
I was thinkin' that bitch Noma
need to feel my pain.
My brother's pain, Tariq.
I mean, weren't you the same one
who was teachin' me
how to revenge better?
Well, lesson fucking learned.
So you fuckin' kill her? You kill her?
Well, until it's your mother
that you gotta bury,
I don't give a fuck what you think.
Listen,
that don't change the fact
that Noma got away, all right?
That was our last fuckin'
chance to get her.
No, it wasn't.
Now she wants revenge.
We can use that.
That bitch ain't goin' nowhere.
How'd it go at Carter's office?
Computer is wiped.
Well, now that's a problem
we could solve.
Here y'all go with this Carter
shit again?
How many fuckin' times I gotta say,
I don't give a fuck
about no dirty cop.
As long as Noma's still breathin'.
Chill the fuck out.
Carter's hands are just as dirty
as Noma's, okay?
He tried to kill Monet, too,
and we barely stopped that shit.
Fuck this.
Listen, I held up my side
of the bargain.
I led y'all niggas to Noma.
Y'all failing is not on me.
But look, I have an advantage
on Carter right now,
and I need to fuckin' make a move
before it's too late.
Wait.
I know you're fucked up.
Yeah, I'll feel a lot better
when this bitch is fuckin' dead.
You can't run off
getting yourself killed
trying to do this on your own, Cane.
What difference does it make?
Until this bitch is in the ground,
nothing or no one else matters to me.
You don't mean that.
I know you got an idea
what his next move is.
Talk to me, please.
He wants me to prove my loyalty to him
by setting you up to die.
Maybe we could use that.
Yeah, you think you could set up
a meeting with Nico for me?
Nico trusts me even less.
Fuck. I'll try.
Bet.
Hey, yo. Hold on.
Hey! Yo, Effie!
Effie, hold on.
We need you for this.
No, I'm not doin' that shit.
What the fuck do you mean,
you're not doin' this shit?
I mean, I'm not doing it.
Always trying to kill somebody new.
Making all these crazy enemies.
It never fucking ends.
Okay, well just remember,
Carter knows about you, too.
So, this affects all of us.
Yeah, I'll take my chances.
Thinking about me now.
I can't do this.
Everything okay?
You already asked me that.
What-what is it?
Dru came through after all.
He's settin' Tariq up,
but he's leaving it up
to you to take the kill shot.
He sent me an address.
You wan't back up?
Nah, I got it.
All right, so I do this for you,
you gonna show me
where Noma is, right?
Where's Tariq?
I don't know, man.
He was fuckin' right here.
Is this your little fuckin' trap Dru?
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
One step ahead of you, my nigga.
Are you out of your fucking mind?
You know what I have on you.
Had, you mean?
That shit is gone now.
I deleted it from the computer myself.
Meaning you got nothin'
left to threaten us with.
Shut up 'fore I slap
the shit out of you.
My task force knows I'm here,
All right?
They know I'm huntin' you. Okay?
No matter how you look at it,
you don't walk away from this baby.
Your task force is fuckin' done.
Oh.
We came to make you an offer, though.
- I'm listening.
- And if you cooperate,
Mhm.
that evidence of you killin'
Kamaal Tate, we destroy it.
You'll walk free, but after that
it has to be understood
that we fuckin' own you.
You fuckin' kids. Yeah.
Okay.
The only piece of
evidence that can prove
that I had anything to do
with that, was a bullet.
I already took care of it, all right?
So, you're too late.
You took care of it?
'Cause this looks a lot
like that bullet, huh?
So let me ask you again.
And this time, I'll make the
deal a little bit sweeter.
You do what the fuck I said,
we put all of this on Detective Nico.
- How about that?
- How?
You say Nico went rogue.
That he was the one behind
all this dirty task force shit.
If I say yes?
You pin the Tate murder on Nico,
and this all goes away.
You just gotta remember
to stay in line.
Yeah.
Stayin' in line.
Ah! Fuckin' Nico.
All right, you give me the evidence,
I'll put the cuffs on Nico myself.
Carter!
The fuck are you doin'?
I'm takin' a fuckin'
cop killer to jail.
Are you fuckin' serious?
You're fuckin' done for, Carter!
Ah, fuck!
You done fucked up.
You know you fucked up, right?
You should wipe those fuckin'
smiles off your faces.
What do you think you got, huh?
A bunch of drug dealers gonna
arrest one of NYPD's finest.
Get the fuck out of here.
I'm a fucking hero in this city.
I'll have each and every one
of you motherfuckers in Rikers
by tonight with a carved
spoon in your fucking neck
while the mayor's puttin'
a fuckin' medal around mine.
This motherfucker!
Do you know who the fuck I am?
Hm.
You were my brother.
You were my fuckin' brother.
We had a code.
Your fucking code!
And you broke it.
I would have followed you to hell.
We all would have,
but you fuckin' betrayed us.
Kate.
Felicia.
You fucking betrayed me!
Nico,
you give 'em the bullet?
Huh?
That's what I thought.
You dug your own fuckin' grave.
You fuckin' did this.
Detective Carter, you are under arrest
for the murder of Officer Kamaal Tate.
Put your hands behind your back.
Don't fuck with me.
You know what it is.
Hands behind your back.
This ain't over.
No, unfortunately for you,
it's definitely over.
She is hurting right now.
We can use that against her.
Took care of Carter.
He'll be rottin' in fuckin'
prison for the rest of his life.
That's it?
Snake is still breathin'?
Uh, prison is worse
than death for a cop.
And discrediting him,
means that any evidence he had
against us
is absolutely fucking useless.
- Any luck on your end?
- We don't know where she is yet-
But we don't need to.
Bring this bitch to us.
How?
A flight plan.
Anytime someone books Noma's jet,
she gets a notification for it.
She'll think we're gonna
take it on the run.
So, set the trap and wait.
Okay. Okay, Cane.
Are you sure about this?
- It's just the three of us left.
- We post up at the hangar.
As soon as she shows her face,
we take the bitch out.
It's only one way in,
so we'll have the fuckin' advantage.
Chinedu, they booked the jet.
If you follow her,
you will be dead by tomorrow
morning, I guarantee you.
What the hell are you doing?
- We are leaving.
- We know where they are.
We need to get to
the airport to cut them off.
Noma, listen to yourself.
This is clearly a trap.
I can't let you go.
I don't need your permission.
And I don't care if it's a trap.
We outgun them 5 to 1.
That family should not get
the privilege to breathe another
breath while Anya can't.
This crusade of yours,
has already cost the lives
of too many of our people.
Before you started this war,
we outnumbered them 10 to 1.
No, we are going to put
an end to this.
I am not going with you.
And neither will our men.
- Fucking coward!
- Ha.
Who the fuck do you think you are?
All of you, fucking cowards!
Do y'all think she'll take the bait?
Yeah, I know she will.
You good?
Yeah.
I'm just thinking Monet would be happy
we're back working together
again as a family.
Mm.
Hey, what's the first thing
you remember her saying
to you as a kid?
Shut your ass up and quit cryin'.
Ah.
- Yeah, that sound like her.
- Yeah.
Mm.
Yeah.
All right look,
don't shoot until we see Noma,
all right?
I don't give a fuck who she's with,
- all guns on her first.
- Bet.
What the fuck?
- Fuck.
- She cannot get away with this.
Listen,
I'm proud of y'all, all right?
And I'm proud to be your brother.
But do what the cops say,
and don't get yourself shot.
Cane, what the fuck are
you talking about?
Come out!
Come out now!
Fuck!
Cane, it's a one way trip.
Don't fuckin' do this, a'ight?
We'll find another way.
Ain't no other way, all right.
Listen to me for once, please.
Don't get yourself shot.
I gotta do this for ma.
All right? Family first.
Family first.
Come out!
- Come out now!
- Okay, we're coming out.
We are unarmed. Don't shoot!
Hands where I can see 'em!
Don't shoot! We are unarmed.
Don't shoot!
Walk to me now, slowly.
On the ground!
Right now! On the ground!
- Put your hands on the ground.
- Okay.
Get down! Cuff him!
Hey!
Ah! All right, all right.
Ah!
Stand up!
Get up! Let's go.
We didn't finish that dance.
Didn't think my face
would be the last one, you see.
Right?
You could have had everything with me.
I had everything.
Monet was everything.
You,
you're nothin'.
No!
Noma turned informant to save herself.
And she thought she could use
the Tejada's as scapegoats.
She was playing you.
Noma was the real target
of your investigation all along.
Dru and Diana Tejada, are innocent.
That still doesn't explain
what they were doing
at the hangar.
Dru and Diana were only trying
to defend themselves from Noma.
They feared for their lives.
That's bullshit.
Uh, if I may.
I think you two are looking
at this the wrong way.
You have a chance at redemption here.
Noma's the big fish you were chasing.
We can help you prove that.
In the end, it'll vindicate
all your past work,
as well as put you back in the game.
And the Tejada's will testify to that,
if, you let them walk.
What about Tariq St. Patrick's
part in this?
We don't have anything to offer you
regarding Mr. St. Patrick.
From what we can tell,
Tariq wasn't involved.
So he just gets to walk?
What about Agent Young's murder?
Okay, now, see,
that was Noma's hitter.
She hired him.
And you can find a paper trail
that leads directly back
to her employee, Obi Okeke.
Likely why Obi fled the country.
Guys, we're giving you Noma
on a silver platter.
She's your Queenpin.
And as a thank you,
I expect you both to,
uh, withdraw
your complaints to the bar.
I want my fucking license back.
Do we have an agreement?
What about Cane Tejada?
- Where is he?
- We don't know.
Maclean and associates doesn't
presently represent him.
Ah!
Oh, hey!
Easy.
Dr. Lee patched you up,
but you still need real help,
so...
- You're lucky you're alive.
- Yeah, well.
I'm just happy the bitch is dead.
But was it worth it?
Cane, your face is all over the news.
- Fuck it.
- No, you don't get it.
I'll be fine.
Every cop in New York is outside
looking for you right now.
You can never show
your face here again.
Yeah, well, I'll figure it out.
Do you have somewhere to go?
'Cause you're gonna need money.
I said I'll figure it out!
I'm sorry.
Some money I've been saving
for my co-term program.
Effie I can't take your money.
How the fuck else are you gonna
get out of here, Cane?
Why are you doing this?
Why the fuck else?
You're like a little fuckin'
charity case right now.
Just consider returning the favor.
I made it once, I can make it again.
It's nothin'.
Thank you.
And um,
um, I promise I'ma pay you back.
I'll pay you back.
I heard from Cane.
He made it out of town.
Dru, what are you doin'?
Monet gave her life for us.
Cane took Noma out for us.
We cannot let that go to waste.
Okay, then we won't.
We'll rebuild the business.
Diana, I'm so done with the business.
I'm so sick of all the death
and destruction.
I...
It's over.
Dru, it doesn't have-
- It doesn't have to be.
- It does for me.
This is the last second
chance I'll ever have.
I gotta make the most of it.
After Monet's service,
I'm taking
that art fellowship in Paris.
I'll do what I want with my life
from now on.
You should do the same.
Hey, I can't lie,
this food look real good.
I know.
I miss these family dinners.
Thank y'all for having me back.
Well, me too.
Now shut up and let's eat.
The greens could use a little
bit more seasoning.
Ma, I got some good news.
I need you to pack your stuff.
Everything in here
because, I'm taking you out of WitSec.
Boy, what are you talking about?
Everything I need
to worry about is gone, Ma.
Noma, gone, Monet, gone.
Everything I said I
was gonna take care of,
I took care of it.
Ending up at the top
is the best revenge, no?
So we-we're going home?
Baby-baby, we're going home.
No, no, no. Not-not exactly, ma.
All right, but listen,
y'all gonna be set up, ma.
You're not gonna have to work.
Yasmin's gonna go to
an amazing school.
She's gonna have a great life.
She's not gonna have
to worry about anything.
But the only thing is,
it's not gonna be in New York,
and I-I won't be able to be there.
Oh, oh, see.
- No!
- Ma-
That is not what we agreed to Tariq.
I can't have a family and be in
the game at the same time, ma.
It doesn't work.
I mean, look at the Tejadas.
Look at Noma and her daughter Anya.
Ma, look at us.
Look at how you're livin' right now.
I can't keep putting the people
that I love in danger, okay?
That makes me vulnerable.
And I'm not doing that anymore.
So what are you saying?
You just never gonna
have your own family?
As long as I'm in the game, no.
No, no, Riq. Listen, baby,
I can't lose you, okay?
Ma, you're not gonna lose me, okay?
And I promise you that. I'll be fine.
Look, I just need to keep y'all safe,
and this is the way, okay?
Just trust me. Please.
Please.
All right. Come here.
- I love you, all right?
- Love you, too, baby.
I'ma lock down the new connect.
Effie, you gonna be overseeing
the colleges,
runnin' shit through CoursePerfect,
like back in the old days.
Bet.
Thank you.
You know, everything I said
I was a dickhead, so.
It's all good. It's whatever.
You good at what you do,
and that's exactly what we need.
But, from now on,
there's a chain of command.
- Everything goes through me.
- Cool.
See ya.
And B, I need you to run
the fight clubs.
You gotta find another band
so we can keep these
underground parties running too.
Yeah. Say less.
Look,
things are gonna change a little bit.
- What do you mean?
- You could work for me,
but, you're not gonna
be my partner no more, B.
'Riq.
Look B, I can't keep
dealing with you fuckin' up
over and over again, bro.
One fuck up and you're out, that's it.
- Fuck that.
- What do you mean, fuck that?
What, you gonna walk away
from the biggest bag
that you'll ever make in your life?
Bro, it's not about the bread.
Okay? I-I did this to build
something on my own
with my fucking brother.
Yeah, and look where that got us.
We gotta work smarter, all right?
Come on, B.
You in or not?
I'm in.
Appreciate you meeting with me.
Davis said you were a busy man.
Make it quick.
I have a business proposal for you.
Mm.
Let me move your product
in New York City,
and I promise you, I'll double
what Noma was movin'.
Why would I trust my business
to a child I don't know?
Who comes to me making promises
that are too big for him to keep.
Well, I already have a network
in place,
ready to move product
all over the city.
My people stay in line.
They know better than to bite
the hand that feeds them.
We don't create any
emotional connections.
We get straight to business.
That's all it's about.
We keep the peace, so the police,
they know to look the other way.
Keep their pockets full,
they let us do our thing.
And overseeing the financials,
is one of New York's finest attorneys.
He keeps the money flowing,
and he keeps it clean.
Well, considering Miss Sullivan
has withdrawn her complaints
towards you,
I think it's fair to say,
this panel can rescind
the suspension of your license.
Congratulations, Mr. Maclean.
Thank you for your confidence.
I would say this is the most robust,
distribution network in the city,
and right now,
all we need is your product
to keep everything running.
And while all of this is
happening, where will you be?
Nowhere.
Look, no one would know
where this product is coming from.
They won't know
where the money's going.
Shit, they won't even know
that we know each other.
After today, you don't even got
to see my face ever again.
Look, the machine is ready to
go as soon as I say go.
- After that, I'm basically-
- A ghost.
Yeah, a ghost.
Yo.
I ain't heard from you in a minute.
Yeah, I do.
Fuck is goin' on though?
A'ight.
Well, tell them niggas
to bring the smoke,
we'll come lay them
the fuck out. Simple.
I mean, come on, we family for life.
Send me the details,
and I'll be there.
I'm on my way.
sync and corrections by awaqeded
www.addic7ed.com